Contact

alicimen9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aliçimen-12979227 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PHP

Typescript

MySQL

Languages

İngilizce (Full Professional)

Ali Çimen

Senior Web Developer

Istanbul, Istanbul, Turkey

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in PHP, Typescript, Javascript, MySQL, Git . Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Computer Engineering from Atılım Üniversitesi.

Experience

Açık Deniz Bilişim Web Developer January 2016 - Present (7 years 1 month) İstanbul, Türkiye

- Php Back End developer

Aksiyon: Corporation - Project Management System

- Typescript Front End developer

Siper Secure Messaging system for Corporations

Globit Global Bilgi Teknolojileri A.S. Software Developer July 2015 - January 2016 (7 months) İstanbul, Türkiye

- · Financial technology, Treasury banking Applications
- · Software developer, Support
- · MLS Market Limit System, Misys Kondor+

Turan Yazılım C++ Developer December 2010 - May 2011 (6 months)

- · Qt C++
- . Qt Animation, Graphics, Transitions Frameworks
- · Mobile app development
- . Mobile and desktop cross platform development

Education

Atılım Üniversitesi

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Engineering